qct.io 2019-06-09

# Quanta Cloud Technology

This privacy policy governs personal information we collect from our customers and online from our website users ("You"), through QCT events, products, services, software, websites, contacts or our relationship with You.

**INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**

We collect various types of Your personal information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, etc. when you

  * attend an event
  * fill out an inquiry form
  * fill out a request form
  * fill out a registration form
  * browse the QCT website. (We also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system.)
  * download a software update
  * share your content with family and friends about QCT products or press

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To customize your experience. (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)
  * Send communications to you (i.e. product safety information, your transactions status, information about products and services available from QCT and its corporate affiliates, promotional offers and surveys.)
  * To improve our products/ or services. (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
  * When QCT is filming and taking photographs at an event location, it may be used in the inclusion of marketing campaigns.  (By entering an event you are giving permission to be filmed and are aware that this footage could be used in media throughout the world. If you do not wished to be photographed or filmed, you may leave the location during filming.)

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION?**

To protect your personal information, we utilize a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your personal Information from becoming inappropriately lost, misused, unauthorized accessed or disclosed, altered or destroyed.

**WHEN DO WE DISCLOSE YOUR INFORMATION?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may also release your information when we believe such release is appropriate or is to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety, or if you violate our Terms of Use. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to a third party for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**THIRD-PARTY LINKS**

We may provide links to other third-party websites and services which are outside our control and not covered by this Privacy Policy. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We encourage you to review the privacy statements posted on those websites you visit.

**CHILDREN’S PRIVACY**

QCT does not knowingly collect information from children under the legal age. If we learn that a child under the legal age has provided us personal information, we will delete the data from our system in accordance with applicable law.

**COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES**

We may use cookies and other similar technologies (collectively “Cookies”) in various services at our website. Cookies collect certain standard information that your browser sends to our website such as your browser type and the address of the website from which you arrived at our website Those Cookies help make your visit to our website easier, more efficient and more valuable by providing you with a customized experience and recognizing you when you return.

You can decide whether or not to accept Cookies. One way you can do this is through your Internet browser’s settings. Most Internet browsers allow some control of most Cookies through the browser settings (Please note that if you use your browser settings to block all Cookies you may not be able to access parts of our web site.).

By accessing and using our services, you consent to the storage of cookies, other local storage technologies, and other information on your devices. You also consent to the access of such cookies, local storage technologies, and information by us.

**CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may modify this privacy policy at any time. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. We encourage You to periodically review this Policy to be informed of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**PRIVACY QUESTIONS**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

Email us through the “[Contact QCT](http://www.qct.io/?route=information/contact)” page on the QCT website.
